{
    "id": "8a2370551eb241aeb993fc127aafdd47",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ...................... ill for a week before they took him to a doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had been",
                "has been",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Has your problem .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "solved",
                "been solved",
                "being solved"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The accused …………………. the verdict with fear and anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "awaited",
                "awaiting",
                "was awaiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A massive outbreak of influenza ..................... in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occurred",
                "occurs",
                "has occurred",
                "had occurred"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................... some of the samples presented to him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was choosing",
                "had chosen",
                "has chosen",
                "chose"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................… some photos to be developed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "had left",
                "was left"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It must ....................... to you that she was simply lying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occur",
                "have occurred",
                "occurred"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They have all ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "invited",
                "been invited",
                "being invited",
                "inviting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................... much of his time reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spend",
                "spends",
                "is spending",
                "has spent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He should be properly .....................… by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dealt of",
                "dealt with",
                "dealt in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}